brokerltd.com 2016-10-21

# BrokerLTD - Privacy policy.

This privacy policy applies to www.brokerltd.com. and the services associated with the site owned and operated by (“brokerltd”, “We”, “Us”).

Pursuant to our Terms of Service, this document describes how we treat personal information related to your use of the Service on our site, including information you provide when using the service. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

We expressly and strictly limit use of the Service to adults over 18 years. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained this age.

Data Collected General Browsing. You can access some parts of the Service without having an Account, in which case only your IP address, country of origin and other non-personal information about your computer or device (such as web requests, browser type, browser language, referring URL, operating system and date and time of requests) will be recorded for log file information, aggregated traffic information and in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content. If you have an Account, this information will also be recorded and may be associated with your Account.

Using the Service with an Account. Creating an Account is required for using many of the features of the Service. We require certain information about you at registration, including your login and password (which you generate), your full name, company name, e-mail address and country. Other optional information may be input by you as well. Your IP address is also recorded automatically whenever you access the Service and may be associated with your Account. Any other information or content you provide us on the Service will be saved and associated with your account, including information such as credit card, bank account number, payment escrow service log-ins and Drivers License number or National ID number that is used for funds transfers, (either to us or from us).

Cookies. When you use the Service, we may send cookies and other related technologies (including "web beacons") to your computer to uniquely identify your browser session and provide you with a better experience on the Service (see “Additional Information Regarding Cookies” for more information). General Data Usage

We may use the information you give us to provide you with certain features and to create a personalized experience on the Service. We may also use that information to operate, maintain and improve features and functionality of the Service.

We use commercially reasonable means to keep your information strictly confidential. However, your information will be shared with other parties in the following situations: Information regarding Your Websites (including its URL, its category and other similar information) will be made available to other users of the Service for the purposes of selling traffic to Your Website or buying traffic from Your Website, as the case may be. We may provide certain information required for fund transfers (either to us or from us) to third-party payment processors depending on the method of transfer you choose. In the circumstances described below under "Disclosures of Information."

We may use your e-mail or other personal information for non-marketing or administrative purposes, including for correspondence and delivery of payments and documents. We may also use e-mail or other personal information to periodically send you marketing information about the Service, however, you may choose to stop receiving this information by notifying us (see “Access and Choice” section below).

Please note that, as with any other content placed on the Internet, any content on Your Websites which you link to on the Service may be viewed by other users of the Service and you are responsible for such content. Additional Information Regarding Cookies

We use cookies on the Service to track your activity on the website, to enable certain features and to generally make your use of the Service better. We use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to store information so that you will not have to re-enter it on future visits, provide personalized content and information, monitor the effectiveness of the Service and monitor aggregate metrics such as the number of visitors and page views.

We have provided below a list of cookies and similar technologies that we use on the Service, including cookies from third parties. Though we will endeavor to keep this list up to date, due to the nature of changing technologies on the internet and our inability to control third-party cookies directly, please note that the list may not be 100% current. If you do not wish for these and any other cookies to track you, we recommend that you use an internet browser which will allow you to disable them.

You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” directory. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

When you use the Service, you may encounter two types of cookies, "first party" cookies that are ours and "third party" cookies which are found in other companies' internet tools which are used in conjunction with the Service to enhance it. First Party Cookies: Name Purpose

PHPSESSID Stores information about the current user session on your computer. Needed for the site to function correctly.

Third Party Cookies: Name Purpose SWIFT_client Stores information about the client of support system. SWIFT_visitor Stores information about the visitor of support system. SWIFT_sessionid80 Stores information about the session of support system. SWIFT_visitorsession Stores information about the visitor's session of support system.

The use of tracking technologies by our service providers, technology partners or other 3rd party assets (such as social media) on the site is not covered by our privacy policy. These 3rd parties may use cookies, clear gifs, images, and scripts to help them better manage their content on our site. We do not have access or control over these technologies. We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers’ or Users’ personally identifiable information.

Disclosures of Information We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell, rent or otherwise distribute your personal information to third parties without your consent.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing a transaction or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us and are contractually obligated to keep your information confidential.

In addition to the above described disclosures, we may be required to release certain data to comply with legal obligations, court orders, subpoenas or in order to investigate fraud and enforce our Terms and other agreements. We may also release certain data to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users and others. This includes providing information to other companies or organizations like the police or governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against or prosecution of any illegal activity, whether or not it is identified in the Terms.

If brokerltd is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

Access and Choice If your personal information changes, you may correct, update, amend, remove, or ask to have it removed by making the change on your user account settings page, by emailing our Customer Support at support@brokerltd.com, submitting a ticket, or by contacting us at the contact information listed below. If you no longer desire our service, you may contact us directly to request the deactivation and or deletion of your account and personal information. We will respond to your request within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at support@brokerltd.com.

Security The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number or bank account number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Any information or content you transmit to us is done at your own risk. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at support@brokerltd.com.

If you have an account on the Service and have a password giving you access to certain parts of the Service, you are responsible for keeping the password confidential. Anyone else with your password may access your Account and other personal information. Third Party Links and Assets

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of brokerltd. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

Our Web site also includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, links to social media pages and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
